<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jfs on</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/contributors/jfs/</link><description>Recent content in jfs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 20:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/contributors/jfs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A bit of statistics</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/a-bit-of-statistics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/a-bit-of-statistics/</guid><description>As you may know, we have an automatic update checker in Aegisub, you may have noticed it telling you about the 2.1.9 release yesterday.
When we check for updates, we also send a little bit of anonymous system information back, to get an idea of what kind of systems Aegisub is being used on. This allows us to make some basic statistics. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few facts:
In the past 35 hours, about 20,000 checks for updates have been made, in other words, Aegisub gets started more than 550 times an hour, or 13,500 times a day, worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 2.1.9 released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.9-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.9-released/</guid><description>Here.
Sorry about the delays.
FAQ:
Q: Why all those delays? A: First it was blamed on laziness. Then, FFmpegSource 2.17 was getting incredibly close to release and it was thought it was best to wait for those. Then when that happened an older problem resurfaced, not having sufficient access to the servers. All of this was finally resolved yesterday.
Q: So what&amp;rsquo;s new? A: Lots of stuff, although most of it is just bug fixes.</description></item><item><title>Call for translators</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/call-for-translators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 03:59:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/call-for-translators/</guid><description>Version 2.1.9 is still getting closer to being ready for release, although there&amp;rsquo;s still some actual issues needing, at the very least, testing.
However, there are some user interface languages we had in 2.1.8 or earlier versions, where the translator has gone missing, or just hasn&amp;rsquo;t responded to my mail.
Catalan (Eduard)
Farsi (Meysam)
Korean (unknown)
Polish (Adam)
Vietnamese (Hung NGUYEN, OnEsChi)</description></item><item><title>Not dead yet</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/not-dead-yet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/not-dead-yet/</guid><description>Aegisub is still alive!
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people asking whether Aegisub is dead, or what is happening, so it&amp;rsquo;s probably a good idea to write an update on it.
First: No, Aegisub is not dead. There is still at least a bit of life left. Version 2.1.9 is being prepared for release right now, and the main blocker for the Windows version right now is getting the user interface translations updated.</description></item><item><title>The old and present: VSFilter</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/the-old-and-present-vsfilter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/the-old-and-present-vsfilter/</guid><description>A short while ago, yet another fork of the VSFilter subtitle renderer has surfaced, introducing more extensions. Let it be clear immediately: Aegisub will not support any new extensions to the ASS subtitle format. We strongly urge you to not use any extensions, and as for why, please read on.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the history of the ASS subtitle format: In 2004, Gabest made the Guliverkli project open source under the GPL license.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 2.1.8 released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.8-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.8-released/</guid><description>It finally happened. About 6 weeks later than planned. We have released Aegisub version 2.1.8.
Download it from www.aegisub.org
So what&amp;rsquo;s new? Not a whole lot, actually. The major news would be that we now have versions for Mac OS X, Linux and other Unix systems. Do note that especially the Mac version is unstable and has several known problems, we consider it alpha quality software.
For the Windows version, the major highlights are:</description></item><item><title>Linking to Aegisub</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/linking-to-aegisub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/linking-to-aegisub/</guid><description>Okay, since Aegisub has had a lot of different websites and lots of different URLs throughout the years, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be time to clear up things a bit.
These are the correct addresses to link to:
Aegisub project in general: www.aegisub.org Downloading Aegisub: www.aegisub.org Discussion forum: forum.aegisub.org This blog: blog.aegisub.org Developers' site (trac): devel.aegisub.org Mailing lists: lists.aegisub.org SVN repository: svn.aegisub.org User manual: docs.aegisub.net - only for 2.1.x versions Two things happened last night: We set up a new, temporary website at www.</description></item><item><title>Getting ready for 2.1.8</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/getting-ready-for-2.1.8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/getting-ready-for-2.1.8/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over three months since we released 2.1.7 stable, and we are happy to announce that version 2.1.8 is getting closer every day.
After we released 2.1.7 we split Aegisub development into two main branches: The stable branch where we apply bugfixes for the last stable version, and the development trunk where we work on grand new features.
For all of you not using Windows we also have some good news.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 2.1.7 released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.7-released/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 13:43:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-2.1.7-released/</guid><description>Finally!
It&amp;rsquo;s been almost a month since the 4 year anniversary and the promise of 2.1.7 &amp;ldquo;within a few days&amp;rdquo;, but lots of stuff happened, people were travelling and otherwise not reachable. But I dare say it&amp;rsquo;s not a bad thing, this version of Aegisub we are releasing now is certainly more polished than what we could have managed four weeks ago.
So far, this release is just for Windows. Use the Download button above to get the new version.</description></item><item><title>Four years of Aegisub</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/four-years-of-aegisub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 17:05:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/four-years-of-aegisub/</guid><description>Today it&amp;rsquo;s just about four years since Aegisub was first conceived.
It was on the 17th of June 2005 in a private channel on the ChatSociety IRC network. We were discussing the various problems with making advanced typesetting in ASS subtitles and how poor the tools generally were.
The original name was Visual SSA, and it was originally just intended to be a tool to assist in doing typesetting. Yes, the visual typesetting tools we only got implemented somewhat in the more recent versions was the original goal of the program.</description></item></channel></rss>