<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aegisub dev Blog on</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Aegisub dev Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3.1.0 beta</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/3.1.0-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/3.1.0-beta/</guid><description>There are still some issues to sort out, but 3.1 is largely complete so I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be good to release a beta version for people to play with. If you encounter crashes or other bugs, please report them at http://devel.aegisub.org/wiki/NewTicket. I cannot fix bugs which I am not aware of. If you have comments or complaints about changes, post them on the forums.
Barring major issues, I hope to release the final version of 3.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.3 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.3-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 04:53:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.3-released/</guid><description>Mostly just some assorted bug fixes, a new UI translation (Dutch), and updates to the Arabic and Finnish translations. As usual the changelog can be found here.
This release is the first one in a while to have an official Linux binary, since Debian still doesn&amp;rsquo;t package any versions of wxWidgets released in the last two years. It&amp;rsquo;s somewhat experimental, but should work on all relatively recent Debian-based Linux distributions (Ubuntu 12.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.1 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.1-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 04:35:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.1-released/</guid><description>This is just a quick maintenance release to package up some updates to the translations which were too late for 3.0.0 and fix some easy-to-fix bugs that were reported after 3.0.0 was released. See the changelog for more details.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.0 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.0-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 16:50:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-3.0.0-released/</guid><description>Back in 2009, it was becoming increasingly clear that Aegisub&amp;rsquo;s code base was becoming an unmaintainable mess, and so following the release of 2.1.7 development was split into two branches: 2.1.8 was to be a minor bug fix release, while 2.2.0 would Fix All The Problems. This, of course, turned out to be wildly overambitious. 2.2.0 ended up involving rewriting substantial portions of the program, and was eventually renamed 3.0.0 (after briefly being 2.</description></item><item><title>A bit of statistics</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/a-bit-of-statistics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/a-bit-of-statistics/</guid><description>As you may know, we have an automatic update checker in Aegisub, you may have noticed it telling you about the 2.1.9 release yesterday.
When we check for updates, we also send a little bit of anonymous system information back, to get an idea of what kind of systems Aegisub is being used on. This allows us to make some basic statistics. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few facts:
In the past 35 hours, about 20,000 checks for updates have been made, in other words, Aegisub gets started more than 550 times an hour, or 13,500 times a day, worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 2.1.9 released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-2.1.9-released/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-2.1.9-released/</guid><description>Here.
Sorry about the delays.
FAQ:
Q: Why all those delays? A: First it was blamed on laziness. Then, FFmpegSource 2.17 was getting incredibly close to release and it was thought it was best to wait for those. Then when that happened an older problem resurfaced, not having sufficient access to the servers. All of this was finally resolved yesterday.
Q: So what&amp;rsquo;s new? A: Lots of stuff, although most of it is just bug fixes.</description></item><item><title>Call for translators</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/call-for-translators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 03:59:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/call-for-translators/</guid><description>Version 2.1.9 is still getting closer to being ready for release, although there&amp;rsquo;s still some actual issues needing, at the very least, testing.
However, there are some user interface languages we had in 2.1.8 or earlier versions, where the translator has gone missing, or just hasn&amp;rsquo;t responded to my mail.
Catalan (Eduard)
Farsi (Meysam)
Korean (unknown)
Polish (Adam)
Vietnamese (Hung NGUYEN, OnEsChi)</description></item><item><title>Not dead yet</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/not-dead-yet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 01:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/not-dead-yet/</guid><description>Aegisub is still alive!
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people asking whether Aegisub is dead, or what is happening, so it&amp;rsquo;s probably a good idea to write an update on it.
First: No, Aegisub is not dead. There is still at least a bit of life left. Version 2.1.9 is being prepared for release right now, and the main blocker for the Windows version right now is getting the user interface translations updated.</description></item><item><title>The old and present: VSFilter</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/the-old-and-present-vsfilter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/the-old-and-present-vsfilter/</guid><description>A short while ago, yet another fork of the VSFilter subtitle renderer has surfaced, introducing more extensions. Let it be clear immediately: Aegisub will not support any new extensions to the ASS subtitle format. We strongly urge you to not use any extensions, and as for why, please read on.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the history of the ASS subtitle format: In 2004, Gabest made the Guliverkli project open source under the GPL license.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 2.1.8 released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-2.1.8-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/blog/aegisub-2.1.8-released/</guid><description>It finally happened. About 6 weeks later than planned. We have released Aegisub version 2.1.8.
Download it from www.aegisub.org
So what&amp;rsquo;s new? Not a whole lot, actually. The major news would be that we now have versions for Mac OS X, Linux and other Unix systems. Do note that especially the Mac version is unstable and has several known problems, we consider it alpha quality software.
For the Windows version, the major highlights are:</description></item></channel></rss>