<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plorkyeran on</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/contributors/plorkyeran/</link><description>Recent content in Plorkyeran on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 03:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/contributors/plorkyeran/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3.1.0 beta</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/3.1.0-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/3.1.0-beta/</guid><description>There are still some issues to sort out, but 3.1 is largely complete so I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be good to release a beta version for people to play with. If you encounter crashes or other bugs, please report them at http://devel.aegisub.org/wiki/NewTicket. I cannot fix bugs which I am not aware of. If you have comments or complaints about changes, post them on the forums.
Barring major issues, I hope to release the final version of 3.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.3 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.3-released/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 04:53:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.3-released/</guid><description>Mostly just some assorted bug fixes, a new UI translation (Dutch), and updates to the Arabic and Finnish translations. As usual the changelog can be found here.
This release is the first one in a while to have an official Linux binary, since Debian still doesn&amp;rsquo;t package any versions of wxWidgets released in the last two years. It&amp;rsquo;s somewhat experimental, but should work on all relatively recent Debian-based Linux distributions (Ubuntu 12.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.1 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.1-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 04:35:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.1-released/</guid><description>This is just a quick maintenance release to package up some updates to the translations which were too late for 3.0.0 and fix some easy-to-fix bugs that were reported after 3.0.0 was released. See the changelog for more details.</description></item><item><title>Aegisub 3.0.0 Released</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.0-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 16:50:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/zh-cn/blog/aegisub-3.0.0-released/</guid><description>Back in 2009, it was becoming increasingly clear that Aegisub&amp;rsquo;s code base was becoming an unmaintainable mess, and so following the release of 2.1.7 development was split into two branches: 2.1.8 was to be a minor bug fix release, while 2.2.0 would Fix All The Problems. This, of course, turned out to be wildly overambitious. 2.2.0 ended up involving rewriting substantial portions of the program, and was eventually renamed 3.0.0 (after briefly being 2.</description></item></channel></rss>