<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aegisub Docs on</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Aegisub Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Main Page</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/main_page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/main_page/</guid><description>Welcome to the Aegisub manual. See our about page for more information on the program, or browse the topics on the left bar.
Documentation related to delopment of Aegisub and building Aegisub is located at the bug tracker.
Starting points # Quick overview of Aegisub
Common tasks:
Timing a translated script to audio Basic typesetting of on-screen signs Putting your finished subtitles onto the video (for viewing or distribution) Translating a subtitle file from one language to another Correcting a subtitle that&amp;rsquo;s not properly synchronised to the video Timing karaoke to a song Creating fancy karaoke effects</description></item><item><title>What is Aegisub?</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/about/</guid><description>Aegisub was originally created as a tool to make typesetting, particularly in anime fansubs, a less painful experience. At the time of the start of the project, many other programs that supported the Advanced Substation Alpha format lacked (and in many cases, still lack; development on several competing programs have since been dropped for various reasons completely unrelated to Aegisub) many vital functions, or were too buggy and/or unreliable to be really useful.</description></item><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/overview/</guid><description>This screenshot shows the Aegisub main window with everything open:
The two most important areas are the Subtitles Grid and Edit Box.
The grid shows all the subtitle lines in the file you&amp;rsquo;re working with. Lines are marked with different colours depending on their properties. For example, lines with green background are selected. Lines with blue background are marked as comments and won&amp;rsquo;t be shown on screen. Lines with a light yellow background are visible on the current video frame.</description></item><item><title>Highlights</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/highlights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/highlights/</guid><description>Some highlights of Aegisub:
Simple and intuitive yet powerful interface for editing subtitles With help from such features as spell checking/thesaurus, a translation assistant, call tips for override tags, syntax highlighting and various macros, translating, editing and quality assuring subtitles is now easier than ever. Made a mistake? Had a system crash? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, Aegisub saves your .ass with features like multi-level undo/redo, auto saving, backups and emergency recovery saving in case of system or program crashes.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/credits/</guid><description>Aegisub was originally written by Rodrigo Braz Monteiro with significant contributions from Niels Martin Hansen. Development was lead by Monteiro through 2008, Hansen through 2010, and by Thomas Goyne from 2011 onward.
Programming # Main Programmers: Rodrigo Braz Monteiro (ArchMage ZeratuL) - Lead developer, video system, audio system, subtitles I/O, tools Niels Martin Hansen (jfs) - Automation, Lua automation, audio system, tools Thomas Goyne (Plorkyeran) - Lead developer for 3.</description></item><item><title>General Disclaimer</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/aegisub_manual/general_disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/aegisub_manual/general_disclaimer/</guid><description>This manual is a work in progress. It is at present incomplete and no information in it can be taken for granted. We attempt to be accurate on every point, to a reasonable degree.
Aegisub is software under constant development. While it is a goal to provide up-to-date documentation there will almost always be cases where the actual functionality of the program has changed since this documentation was last updated.</description></item><item><title>Support Aegisub</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/support/</guid><description>Do you want to support Aegisub? Well, it&amp;rsquo;s easy!
Feedback # You can give us feedback - comments, critiques, suggestions, etc. Bug reports and feature requests are always welcome. Check out our forums and the bug tracker, or stop by for a chat in the IRC channel.
Spreading the word # Like Aegisub? Tell your friends about it! Spreading the word is a good way of helping Aegisub to be the best subtitle editor around.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/faq/</guid><description>A small collection of Frequently Asked Questions about Aegisub - mostly stuff that didn&amp;rsquo;t fit anywhere else.
Karaoke effects? # See the Karaoke Templater tutorials.
Can I create DVD subtitles with Aegisub? # Not directly, but there&amp;rsquo;s a nifty program called MaestroSBT that can convert SSA to VOBSubs. It does have quite a bunch of restrictions on what tags and other things may be used, so reading its manual first is advised.</description></item><item><title>Tutorials</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/tutorials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/tutorials/</guid><description>The following tutorials are available for Aegisub:
Video Tutorials (Screencasts) # Dialogue Timing # Description: A video describing how to time using Aegisub.
By: Karl Blomster
Link: http://mod16.org/aegisub/timingtutorialimprovisation.mkv
Description: A video showing an experienced user timing at full speed in Aegisub.
By: Karl Blomster
Link: http://mod16.org/aegisub/timing-fullspeed.mkv
Kanji Timer # Description: A video tutorial demonstrating how the kanji timer can be used to synchronize kanji timing to romaji timing.</description></item><item><title>Karaoke Timing Tutorial</title><link>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/karaoke_timing_tutorial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aegisub.github.io/aegisite/docs/3.2/karaoke_timing_tutorial/</guid><description>This tutorial will teach you how to load a song into Aegisub, how to enter the words for the song and how to add time-codes to the words to synchronise them with the song.
You don&amp;rsquo;t need to have used Aegisub before to follow this tutorial.
Before we begin # There&amp;rsquo;s a few things you need to have ready before starting:
The song itself. This can for example be as an MP3 file or inside a video.</description></item></channel></rss>